Tang Zhiluo.
Kill Yuwen Jingxuan.
I don't know why
you appeared again.
Since I have found you,
I won't allow you to be in any danger.
My Lord,
could you inform me earlier next time you venture into the tiger's den alone?
If I hadn't arrived in time
and you had died there,
the Crown Prince's investiture next month would be canceled,
saving the Ministry of Revenue some silver.
Are you that eager to find another job?
You want to get rid of me?
In your dreams.
I was impulsive.
You always die and are reborn.
How many times has it been?
You must have forgotten everything again.
No matter how many times you go through the cycle of life and death,
you must return to my side.
Tang Zhiluo.
Did you hear me?
The human monarch has appeared in the world.
You must go to his side
and fulfill your mission.
Protect him. Kill him.
Assist him. Kill him.
Remember, kill him.
Protect him.
Assist him.
Kill Yuwen Jingxuan.
Protect him.
Kill him. Assist him.
Zhiluo.
You're awake.
Yuwen Jingxuan.
Kill him.
Kill Yuwen Jingxuan.
Zhiluo.
She must have been hit by the Soul-Destroying Nail,
which is why she lost her mind
and is acting abnormally.
No wonder she attacked me.
The Soul-Destroying Nail is a forbidden art of the Shang clan,
passed down only to the eldest legitimate child.
Are you really going to the Yuwen clan's forbidden area to exchange for the antidote?
I must go.
Can you not go?
The crown prince ceremony is imminent.
We can't fail at the last moment.
Are you saying this as a friend
or as an advisor?
As a friend,
I completely understand your feelings for her all these years.
But as an advisor,
I hope you don't go.
Don't worry.
Even if I die,
you and the Su family will be able to retreat safely.
Am I advising you for myself
or for my Su family?
You know it's a trap.
Su Zhiye.
You are my best friend.
If she wakes up,
help me take care of her.
Tell me, what do you want?
Anything?
Is that woman so important to you?
Okay.
I want your...
Miss Tang!
Are you alright, Miss Tang?
Miss Tang! Miss Tang!
Miss Tang!
Miss Tang! Young Master Su!
You are too cruel.
Even if you blame me,
there's nothing I can do.
If she really broke her arm,
Jingxuan would definitely fight me to the death.
Miss Tang, Miss Tang.
It's okay.
It's okay, Miss Tang.
Jingxuan.
Let me do it.
I really don't know what to do with you.
Who are you?
I am Yuwen Jingxuan.
Then...
who am I?
This inspection of river affairs
and investigation of corruption
have been applauded by everyone in the court and the public.
My father's letter said
Prince Yu looked very displeased,
and His Majesty was not very happy either.
His Majesty has always been biased.
Don't take it to heart.
I didn't expect anything anyway.
There are plenty of discerning people,
so my political achievements won't be buried.
Just mentioning it makes me angry for you.
He disliked the late Empress,
and consequently, he harshly suppresses you.
Haven't you suffered enough grievances all these years?
You and Prince Yu share the same roots.
He was born to the second empress,
and is beneath you.
You face obstacles in everything,
while he has smooth sailing.
I really can't accept this.
Even five fingers are not of the same length.
Pass a message to the Right Chancellor for me.
In the court,
there is no need to engage in verbal disputes.
Yes,
my Prince Shuo.
Someone fell into the water!
Hey, Jingxuan!